[Music]
foreign
I am from Gabriel
[Music]
hello my name is Aditya Verma I'm 21
years old and I'm currently pursuing
b-tech in computer science from
maharashima condition for team to be
University as a George Washington Carver
said education is the key to unlock the
golden door of spring
share my attitude achieved all of you I
got placed at capgem night I just hope
as analyst and all the credit goes to my
teacher as they helped me in getting
ready for the real world actually I was
very underconfident person who don't
know how to explore new things but the
culture and environment of this
University had changed me a lot our
university has organized a specific
training programs industry standards
that helped me a lot to get placement
offer on a CO I want to thank my
university for arranging special
training programs which helped me a lot
to grab this great opportunity
I won't be necessary skills required to
clear the company specific exams I'd
like to be the part of this whole team
whatever I have achieved till now is
because of them thanks to the staff and
my friends for being supportive for me
and a big thanks to my parents to give
me a chance to study at mmdu and of
course Maharishi markande showed him to
be University thanks to mmdu
[Music]